<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Web | Nest]]></title>
  <link href="http://weshui.github.io/blog/categories/web/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://weshui.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-06-15T20:30:56-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://weshui.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Wesley Hui]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Setup Your Own Domain Name on Github]]></title>
    <link href="http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/06/11/how-to-setup-your-own-dns-on-github/"/>
    <updated>2014-06-11T15:24:23-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/06/11/how-to-setup-your-own-dns-on-github</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Github provides such a great hosting service free of charge, too bad that the domain name is default to be</p>

<pre><code>http://github_id.github.io
</code></pre>

<p>Indeed, we programmers tend to &ldquo;show off&rdquo; our knowledges in anthing-related-to-computer, so it&rsquo;s often the case that we use our own domain name instead. For easy memorization and, of course, the bragging right.</p>

<p>Here in this post, I will walk through the topic on how to set up your own domain name on Github. Main reason I want to do this is because I found the turtial online is kinda confusing. I will try to explain it in a plain english manner.</p>

<p>If you don&rsquo;t quite understand the concept, here is a good <a href="https://support.google.com/a/answer/48090?hl=en">link</a> that explains everything concept you need to know before get it stared.</p>

<blockquote><p>Step 1, get a domain name</p></blockquote>

<p>Yes, you have to buy one and all the domain names come with price. For example, this website&rsquo;s domain name is 10 dollors/year, not that bad if you think about it. You can buy domain name from <strong>domain name registrar</strong>, <a href="https://www.godaddy.com/">GoDaddy</a>, <a href="https://www.namecheap.com/">namecheap</a> just to name a few. For consistency, let&rsquo;s say you register a domain name <strong>yourdomain.com</strong> on Namecheap. (Note, this tutorial is for APEX domain name. Subdomains should be able to follow most of the steps until but not include step 4)</p>

<blockquote><p>Step 2, host your website on Github</p></blockquote>

<p>For details on how to host your website on github, here is the <a href="https://pages.github.com/">link</a>. Create repository and push it. Simple enough. By now, you should have a repository called <em>github_id.github.io</em></p>

<blockquote><p>Step 3, push a file named CNAME into your respository</p></blockquote>

<p>Create a file in your <em>github_id.github.io</em> repository called <strong>CNAME</strong>. There should be only one line in this newly create file, that is <strong>youdomain.com</strong>. Push this file to Github and make sure it exists under root directory.</p>

<blockquote><p>Step 4, redirect your domain name to Github</p></blockquote>

<p>Go to your account where you registered your domain name, select your domain name and under the <strong>Host Management</strong> tab (or similar tab), click <strong>All Host Records</strong>. By default, top should have two records, one as <strong>@</strong> and one as <strong>www</strong>. Change them to :</p>

<pre><code>@       192.30.252.154    A(Address)    n/a    1800
www     yourdomain.com    URL Redirect  n/a    1800
</code></pre>

<p>In the sub-domain settings, we need to add another record(thanks to github) that redirect the host to Github server, it looks like</p>

<pre><code>@       192.30.252.153    A(Address)    n/a    1800 
</code></pre>

<p>Save this settings.</p>

<blockquote><p>Step 5, wait until it comes up</p></blockquote>

<p>Github can take time to configure these settings, so be patience. To test the host, we can use the methods described in the tutotial.</p>

<pre><code>dig yourdomain.com +nostats +nocomments +nocmd
</code></pre>

<p>if the IP addresses show up are precisely 192.30.252.154 and 192.30.252.153(if everything is normal, both should show up), we are good to go!</p>

<p>This is the tutorial for setting up APEX domain name on github, buf if you have a subdomain name, for example <strong>www.yourdomain.com</strong> instead of <strong>yourdomain.com</strong>, your don&rsquo;t need to create A record. Just redirect the www url to <strong>your_id.github.io</strong> should do the trick.</p>

<p>Here is the original link to the <a href="https://help.github.com/articles/setting-up-a-custom-domain-with-github-pages">turotial</a> Github provides.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
