<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Projects | Wes's Matrix]]></title>
  <link href="http://weshui.github.io/blog/categories/projects/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://weshui.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2016-06-16T22:29:54-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://weshui.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Wesley Hui]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[wesely92@gmail.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Project Ivy Part1]]></title>
    <link href="http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/06/09/project-ivy-part1/"/>
    <updated>2014-06-09T09:58:47-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/06/09/project-ivy-part1</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Fortunately,  Ivy still seems unaware of what I&rsquo;ve been doing recently. Everytime she asked &ldquo;What are you doing for the night?&rdquo;, I answered &ldquo;Coding&rdquo;. I know she probably will never find this website until I tell her. Can&rsquo;t wait to see what she will response to this =P</p>

<p>I have several possible outlines for this project. But it seems an awesome website with customized video recap for the past year would be the most-likely one to literally make her burst into tears (Evil me). For the credit, I got this idea from <a href="https://www.facebook.com/lookback">Facebook Lookback</a>. I like your work Facebook, so please don&rsquo;t sue me.</p>

<p>In order to do that, I need many tools/programms:</p>

<pre><code>Photo Editing Software
Video Editing Software
Photo Mosaic (Plan to write one)
Photo Fetcher from Facebook (Plan to write one)
Bootstrap + Good JS libaray to make website neat(possibly Angular.js)
TBA
</code></pre>

<p>Cool stuff and a tons of learning experiences and potential opportunity to impress girl friend.</p>

<h1>Be A Good Programmer Plus Boyfriend</h1>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Project Ivy Init]]></title>
    <link href="http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/06/02/project-ivy-init/"/>
    <updated>2014-06-02T20:54:05-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/06/02/project-ivy-init</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I met with my girlfriend Ivy when we were both students in University of Illinois at Urbana Champaign. She was a master candidate majoring in Econ, and I was a 屌丝(Diaosi, Chinese Charactors, roughly translate into &ldquo;a nerdy guy who everyone knows will not get a girl friend&rdquo;) in Math &amp; Computer Science.</p>

<p>Oct 2 of 2014 is our 1st year anniversary, and right now we are on skype while I&rsquo;m typing this blog.</p>

<p>She must not know the following project details as this will be my suprise gift for her.</p>

<p>I will launch a website with customized domain name, hosted on github. In the website, I will do some cool stuff (TBD, but have some cool ideas) to impress her. The website will be on <a href="http://wes-ivy.me">http://wes-ivy.me</a> , which currently redirects to this blog.</p>

<p>How likely she will find out about this intent? Hmm, statistically highly unlikely. She is just a normal girl who can&rsquo;t distinguish Mac OS &amp; iOS =P</p>

<p>This project will be a whole learning experience for me as well. I&rsquo;ve done Bootstrap before, but to really do what I have in mind requires far more than playing around.</p>

<p>I have 4 months, lets go and see.</p>

<p>Will post more updates later.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
