<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Wes's Matrix]]></title>
  <link href="http://weshui.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://weshui.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-05-07T16:08:28+08:00</updated>
  <id>http://weshui.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Wesley Hui]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Good Stuff]]></title>
    <link href="http://weshui.github.io/blog/2015/05/07/some-good-stuff/"/>
    <updated>2015-05-07T15:51:38+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://weshui.github.io/blog/2015/05/07/some-good-stuff</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Rencently, I&rsquo;m studying Java in depth (after the realization that I was playing rather than using it).</p>

<p>Some good websites in case someone in the near future ask you similar questions:</p>

<ul>
<li><h3>Java-related:</h3>

<ul>
<li><a href="http://eclipsesource.com/blogs/2012/09/04/the-3-things-you-should-know-about-hashcode/">Why you should rewrite hashcode</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><h3>Math-related:</h3>

<ul>
<li><a href="http://preshing.com/20110504/hash-collision-probabilities/">Probability of Hash collision (I like the math here, bring back old times lol)</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Back to China!]]></title>
    <link href="http://weshui.github.io/blog/2015/03/05/back-to-china/"/>
    <updated>2015-03-05T15:46:42+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://weshui.github.io/blog/2015/03/05/back-to-china</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>It&rsquo;s been a while before I realize my last post was last year Nov 18.</p>

<p>I agree with you, I&rsquo;m lazy~</p>

<p>Anyway, many things happended over the past few mothes, and I would like to write them down (So I can refer to it years after).</p>

<ol>
<li><p>I got another gradute school admission offer from University of Wisconsin-Madison. TA position plus scholarship. Way better package thane the UCLA one. Yet, I have not decided where I should go for graduate school.</p></li>
<li><p>I decided to spend the next 6 months in Hangzhou China for the following reasons: a) I believe family is very important, b) my working authorization expired (which I could extend, but I didn&rsquo;t).</p></li>
<li><p>Before going back to China, I spent my past 10 days in New Zealand. Thats right, New Zealand, the first country to see the sunrise. In fact, this post is writen in Auckland International Airport, where I have 2 hours before boarding the plane to Shanghai.</p></li>
<li><p>I definitely will go back to U.S. for graudate school later this year. Which school? Not quite clear yet.</p></li>
</ol>


<p>I&rsquo;m back, China!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hover Board for Real]]></title>
    <link href="http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/11/19/hover-board-for-real/"/>
    <updated>2014-11-19T03:21:01+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/11/19/hover-board-for-real</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Couple of monthes ago, I saw video(starring Tony Hawk) entitled &ldquo;Hover board&rdquo;.</p>

<p>But, it was a hoax.</p>

<p>Now, this time the real &ldquo;Conan&rdquo; board staring the very same person.</p>

<p>Check this out</p>

<div class="embed-video-container"><iframe src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/HSheVhmcYLA" allowfullscreen></iframe></div>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Grad School Admission]]></title>
    <link href="http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/11/19/first-grad-school-admission/"/>
    <updated>2014-11-19T03:17:08+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/11/19/first-grad-school-admission</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Last week, I received my first grad school admission offer!</p>

<p>Master of Science in Computer Science admission from UCLA(for those who don&rsquo;t know, University of California Los Angeles!)</p>

<p>California, I&rsquo;m coming!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Anniversary]]></title>
    <link href="http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/10/03/first-anniversary/"/>
    <updated>2014-10-03T02:43:37+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/10/03/first-anniversary</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>这篇文章是写给妹纸看的，所以还是用中文比较好。</p>

<p>亲爱的WZ姐姐</p>

<p><img class="right" src="https://fbcdn-sphotos-g-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xpa1/v/t1.0-9/10452355_555059154603770_5262808059192557325_n.jpg?oh=4e983214c699c84d7882ca7c4e299472&oe=54C07048&__gda__=1422391536_6caf5429b0c48a39ef82e5c3a0626294" width="280" height="180">
下午工作的时候想起来，今天已经是10/2了。<br>
去年的这个时候，还是学生的我们在一起了。<br>
于是现在已经一年了。<br>
1年里，谢谢你的包容，理解，体贴（if any）。<br>
未来谁也不好说，但是不管在哪，2013年到2014年的这1年我肯定是不会忘记的。<br>
いろいろとありがとうございます!<br>
本来呢，打算这个网站的主页换成一个WebGL的动画的。<br>
但是吧，各种事情和GRE搞的我学习WebGL的过程异常的缓慢。<br>
不过呢，这个网站的网址就当我给你的礼物了。<br>
我自己注册的，是不是很厉害。<br>
顺带一提，ivy-wes这个也是我注册的，会重新导到这里来。<br>
明年的这个时候，WebGL应该可以完工啦，到时候记得来看哈。<br></p>

<p>最后，</p>

<p>周年纪念！<br>
Happy Anniversary！<br>
記念日おめでとう！<br></p>

<p>By Wesley Hui.<br>
All right reserved.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Is Cool]]></title>
    <link href="http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/09/19/this-is-cool/"/>
    <updated>2014-09-19T01:10:35+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/09/19/this-is-cool</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>You think Google Glass is cool? (it is without doubt)</p>

<p>Check out this video</p>

<div class="embed-video-container"><iframe src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/YI5uXlTnNms" allowfullscreen></iframe></div>


<p>I heard that Steve Jobs spends at least half an hour on meditation every day.</p>

<p>Calm down your mind and stay focus.</p>

<p>I want to see how my brain works, might will buy one of this. Definitely cheaper then Google Glass.</p>

<p>PS: thanks Mashable for sharing this news.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[After Roadtrip]]></title>
    <link href="http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/09/11/after-roadtrip/"/>
    <updated>2014-09-11T13:13:03+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/09/11/after-roadtrip</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Well, it&rsquo;s been a while without blogging anything.
The reason for that is, of course, ROAD TRIP.</p>

<p>I have to keep this blogging thing away from my girlfriend. Otherwise, it won&rsquo;t be a suprise gift. Right?</p>

<p>Couple of updates.</p>

<blockquote><p>California is a beautiful place.</p></blockquote>

<p>I&rsquo;ve been to San Fransico and L.A before, but I didn&rsquo;t rent a car back then. This time, we rent car and visited Yosemite (yeah, next version of Mac OS X). In general, CA is an awesome place.</p>

<p>For those of you haven&rsquo;t get a chance to really appreciate CA, this video is good for you.</p>

<div class="embed-video-container"><iframe src="http://player.vimeo.com/video/105286558 "></iframe></div>


<blockquote><p>I passed the interview, but no offer? What? Seriously?</p></blockquote>

<p>I actually interviewed with CapitalOne for a Data Engineer role in their plano office. The first day after interview, my point of contact told me I passed the interview and congrats. Cool. But two days after, she said they need to make an exception to give me offer because my situation is not expected (OPT/F1). Well, why did you interview me in the first place?</p>

<blockquote><p>New AppleEvent</p></blockquote>

<p>Hmm, I will not get Apple Watch. 350$ for a not that impressive watch. Not worth it. But iPhone 6 is actually something. The power of NFC is &ldquo;Massive&rdquo; by one of my colleages. If Apple will release a NFC SDK, it will be Apple&rsquo;s Victory.</p>

<p>Lastly, I just want to see what&rsquo;s the reaction of my girlfriend once she sees this website.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Goodjob Facebook]]></title>
    <link href="http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/08/15/goodjob-facebook/"/>
    <updated>2014-08-15T04:18:12+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/08/15/goodjob-facebook</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Wow, the ice buckget challenge is on heat !</p>

<p>People @ Facebook are crazy.
Nice place to work &amp; nice people to meet</p>

<h1>strikeoutALS</h1>

<p>Link to the people in facebook. Might need login credential, but yeah most browsers store that in cache (not session).</p>

<p><a href="https://www.facebook.com/photo.php?v=10154468167095177&amp;set=vb.717545176&amp;type=2&amp;theater">https://www.facebook.com/photo.php?v=10154468167095177&amp;set=vb.717545176&amp;type=2&amp;theater</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cool Hyperlapse by MSFT Research]]></title>
    <link href="http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/08/13/cool-hyperlapse-by-msft-research/"/>
    <updated>2014-08-13T01:55:09+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/08/13/cool-hyperlapse-by-msft-research</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Its been a while not posting anything. Well, now I&rsquo;m back =D</p>

<p>This is pretty cool stuff.</p>

<p>Despite its fails(unwise decisions) in many other fields recent years(Win Phone, Xbox, some Nokia), Microsoft Research is still delivering astonishing good stuff. Check out this video. Its a awesome way to use augumented reality =D</p>

<p>Good job MSFT Research</p>

<div class="embed-video-container"><iframe src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/SOpwHaQnRSY" allowfullscreen></iframe></div>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[July/15]]></title>
    <link href="http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/07/16/july-slash-15/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-16T02:58:59+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/07/16/july-slash-15</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Finally visited Hogwarts and Diagon Alley and brought wand for myself.</p>

<p>As a loyal Harry Potter Serise fan, I gotta say Orlando trip was amazing. Well done Universal Studio.</p>

<p>Now, got back to deal with Hadoop stuff.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Upcoming Orlando Trip &amp; Misc]]></title>
    <link href="http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/06/25/upcoming-orlando-trip-and-misc/"/>
    <updated>2014-06-25T03:54:59+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/06/25/upcoming-orlando-trip-and-misc</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Booked our trip to Orlando the coming July 4th. Can&rsquo;t wait to see the &ldquo;refurbished&rdquo; Harry Potter Theme Park. I grew up reading Harry Potter series (countless nights in bed and thus shortsightedness). Finally get a chance to get myself a wand and drink butterbeer.</p>

<p>But, as always, you can&rsquo;t be happy and lucky all the time. Just turned down by Zillow for a Softwere Engineer Position. Well, I really like Seattle area and have a bunch of friends in there now. Too bad can&rsquo;t go there for on-site nor further career. A bit-manipulation interview question got me. I haven&rsquo;t use &amp; | ^ for years. Quite suprised that a well-known company actually will ask you this except the classic Two-Int-Exchange-Value question. Anyway, need to practice more on code.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Fire Phone]]></title>
    <link href="http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/06/19/amazon-fire-phone/"/>
    <updated>2014-06-19T08:43:54+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/06/19/amazon-fire-phone</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Spent hours watching Amazon event live today with CNET.</p>

<p>Gotta say Fire Phone&rsquo;s dynamic perceptive is pretty &ldquo;Amazing&rdquo; at first glance. Imaging you can show off that to your friends =D</p>

<div class="embed-video-container"><iframe src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/iB75HJe8eiI" allowfullscreen></iframe></div>


<p>Very cool at first glance, right?</p>

<p>Except that, I don&rsquo;t quite see many &ldquo;Amazing&rdquo; things. Firefly? the app that can recognize everything? Well, apparently I don&rsquo;t want to buy everything from Amazon =D Joking around, the app is clearly to promote to Shop on Amazon, which I don&rsquo;t quite agree that most people will buy. Maybe its a whole new experience for Amazon-mania, but Amazon is not Apple.</p>

<p>Jump to it&rsquo;s price, 300 bucks for a contract phone just to showoff 3D Lock Screen? Let me think&hellip; Nope</p>

<p>Nice try Mr. Benzos. But I will switch to iPhone 6 most likely.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Air Type]]></title>
    <link href="http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/06/16/air-type/"/>
    <updated>2014-06-16T08:58:40+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/06/16/air-type</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Check out this cool startup in Autsin, TX.</p>

<p>Keyboard-less typing!</p>

<p>I think they kinda have to train &ldquo;it&rdquo; (machine learning) so &ldquo;it&rdquo; can recongnize different gesture. Would make more sense if using Online Learning (since everyone has a different way to type, so the keyboard can adjust itself).</p>

<p>Imaging using this for your ipad. Would like to sign-up for beta =D</p>

<p>Link to their <a href="http://airtype.io/concept/">website</a></p>

<div class="embed-video-container"><iframe src="http://player.vimeo.com/video/90766615 "></iframe></div>



]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Setup Your Own Domain Name on Github]]></title>
    <link href="http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/06/12/how-to-setup-your-own-dns-on-github/"/>
    <updated>2014-06-12T04:24:23+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/06/12/how-to-setup-your-own-dns-on-github</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Github provides such a great hosting service free of charge, too bad that the domain name is default to be</p>

<pre><code>http://github_id.github.io
</code></pre>

<p>Indeed, we programmers tend to &ldquo;show off&rdquo; our knowledges in anthing-related-to-computer, so it&rsquo;s often the case that we use our own domain name instead. For easy memorization and, of course, the bragging right.</p>

<p>Here in this post, I will walk through the topic on how to set up your own domain name on Github. Main reason I want to do this is because I found the turtial online is kinda confusing. I will try to explain it in a plain english manner.</p>

<p>If you don&rsquo;t quite understand the concept, here is a good <a href="https://support.google.com/a/answer/48090?hl=en">link</a> that explains everything concept you need to know before get it stared.</p>

<blockquote><p>Step 1, get a domain name</p></blockquote>

<p>Yes, you have to buy one and all the domain names come with price. For example, this website&rsquo;s domain name is 10 dollors/year, not that bad if you think about it. You can buy domain name from <strong>domain name registrar</strong>, <a href="https://www.godaddy.com/">GoDaddy</a>, <a href="https://www.namecheap.com/">namecheap</a> just to name a few. For consistency, let&rsquo;s say you register a domain name <strong>yourdomain.com</strong> on Namecheap. (Note, this tutorial is for APEX domain name. Subdomains should be able to follow most of the steps until but not include step 4)</p>

<blockquote><p>Step 2, host your website on Github</p></blockquote>

<p>For details on how to host your website on github, here is the <a href="https://pages.github.com/">link</a>. Create repository and push it. Simple enough. By now, you should have a repository called <em>github_id.github.io</em></p>

<blockquote><p>Step 3, push a file named CNAME into your respository</p></blockquote>

<p>Create a file in your <em>github_id.github.io</em> repository called <strong>CNAME</strong>. There should be only one line in this newly create file, that is <strong>youdomain.com</strong>. Push this file to Github and make sure it exists under root directory.</p>

<blockquote><p>Step 4, redirect your domain name to Github</p></blockquote>

<p>Go to your account where you registered your domain name, select your domain name and under the <strong>Host Management</strong> tab (or similar tab), click <strong>All Host Records</strong>. By default, top should have two records, one as <strong>@</strong> and one as <strong>www</strong>. Change them to :</p>

<pre><code>@       192.30.252.154    A(Address)    n/a    1800
www     yourdomain.com    URL Redirect  n/a    1800
</code></pre>

<p>In the sub-domain settings, we need to add another record(thanks to github) that redirect the host to Github server, it looks like</p>

<pre><code>@       192.30.252.153    A(Address)    n/a    1800 
</code></pre>

<p>Save this settings.</p>

<blockquote><p>Step 5, wait until it comes up</p></blockquote>

<p>Github can take time to configure these settings, so be patience. To test the host, we can use the methods described in the tutotial.</p>

<pre><code>dig yourdomain.com +nostats +nocomments +nocmd
</code></pre>

<p>if the IP addresses show up are precisely 192.30.252.154 and 192.30.252.153(if everything is normal, both should show up), we are good to go!</p>

<p>This is the tutorial for setting up APEX domain name on github, buf if you have a subdomain name, for example <strong>www.yourdomain.com</strong> instead of <strong>yourdomain.com</strong>, your don&rsquo;t need to create A record. Just redirect the www url to <strong>your_id.github.io</strong> should do the trick.</p>

<p>Here is the original link to the <a href="https://help.github.com/articles/setting-up-a-custom-domain-with-github-pages">turotial</a> Github provides.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Project Ivy Part1]]></title>
    <link href="http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/06/10/project-ivy-part1/"/>
    <updated>2014-06-10T00:58:47+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/06/10/project-ivy-part1</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Fortunately,  Ivy still seems unaware of what I&rsquo;ve been doing recently. Everytime she asked &ldquo;What are you doing for the night?&rdquo;, I answered &ldquo;Coding&rdquo;. I know she probably will never find this website until I tell her. Can&rsquo;t wait to see what she will response to this =P</p>

<p>I have several possible outlines for this project. But it seems an awesome website with customized video recap for the past year would be the most-likely one to literally make her burst into tears (Evil me). For the credit, I got this idea from <a href="https://www.facebook.com/lookback">Facebook Lookback</a>. I like your work Facebook, so please don&rsquo;t sue me.</p>

<p>In order to do that, I need many tools/programms:</p>

<pre><code>Photo Editing Software
Video Editing Software
Photo Mosaic (Plan to write one)
Photo Fetcher from Facebook (Plan to write one)
Bootstrap + Good JS libaray to make website neat(possibly Angular.js)
TBA
</code></pre>

<p>Cool stuff and a tons of learning experiences and potential opportunity to impress girl friend.</p>

<h1>Be A Good Programmer Plus Boyfriend</h1>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[On WWDC14]]></title>
    <link href="http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/06/05/on-wwdc14/"/>
    <updated>2014-06-05T06:50:06+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/06/05/on-wwdc14</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Finished the recap for WWDC 2014 yesterday. Didn&rsquo;t get a chance to write some of my thoughts on it until today.</p>

<p>Every summer, Google-Apple-Microsoft, the big 3 will host a serise of conferences to &ldquo;show off&rdquo; their latest work. Microsoft don&rsquo;t really draw a lot attention and I personally don&rsquo;t like its product (despite the fact that I do have a Nokia phone, but it does not run very smoothly and I don&rsquo;t appreciate that). So, it&rsquo;s quite interesting to watch Apple WWDC vs. Google I/O each year.</p>

<p>Despite its length (more than 2 hrs), I can see 3 major points from WWDC.</p>

<pre><code>Mac OS X Yosemite
iOS 8
Swift (not Taylor)
</code></pre>

<p>The following are my thoughts on each:</p>

<p>Start with <strong>Yosemite</strong>. I&rsquo;m not quite &ldquo;amazed&rdquo; by this except probably its name. (Dan, never been to Yosemite before but will do in this year.) Updates include a lot &ldquo;easier to use&rdquo; features. I will love the features like Mark for email and the new notification ctr where you can put widgets. But still, these new updates do not quite catch my eye when I was watching the video. It&rsquo;s Apple with Tim but only these updates this year? Not stress on performance/batter-life/compability? Well, let&rsquo;s wait and see then.</p>

<p><strong>iOS 8</strong> don&rsquo;t have a lot things as well. Honestly, group-chatting/file-sharing/voice-messge have been out there for years (Yes, I&rsquo;m talking about <a href="http://www.wechat.com/en/">WeChat</a>/QQ, which dominate China). I guess next step for iOS is to have it&rsquo;s own version of moment(a social sharing function built-in WeChat) maybe? One good thing is the tunnel between iOS and Mac OS X is finally opened. I&rsquo;ve been expecting this for quite a while. The continuity is not a quite new stuff. Last time I heard about this concept is from Netflix, where you can pick-up where you left on video across different platforms. And, it should work well with the large amount of Mac/iOS devices out there. What&rsquo;s next? Continuity on apps? Wait, this actually could work. You are welcome Apple.</p>

<p>Finally, <strong>Swift/DevCenter</strong>. As a developer, I gotta say Apple you did a great job here. The ability to use different services from different apps could make our lifes so much easier (both developer and consumer). And the new kits for Graphic looks so cool. 3D kit for casual game? Thats a good idea. Not to mention the new Swift language. Even tho it might be a little bit offend (I know what I&rsquo;m coding, thank you, I don&rsquo;t need to see it, just go away Swift!), but it definitely will help in most of the circumanstances. Wow, this new SDK is quite amazing! Can&rsquo;t wait to start writing my apps, but ya, need to read that 500 pages Swift book first&hellip;=P</p>

<p>And, last but not least, no words for iPhone 6. Gosh, I&rsquo;m waiting for a year but not a single word. (Don&rsquo;t look at me like this, Nokia. Maybe we should just be friends)</p>

<p>Let&rsquo;s see what Google I/O will bring =)</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Project Ivy Init]]></title>
    <link href="http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/06/03/project-ivy-init/"/>
    <updated>2014-06-03T11:54:05+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/06/03/project-ivy-init</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I met with my girlfriend Ivy when we were both students in University of Illinois at Urbana Champaign. She was a master candidate majoring in Econ, and I was a 屌丝(Diaosi, Chinese Charactors, roughly translate into &ldquo;a nerdy guy who everyone knows will not get a girl friend&rdquo;) in Math &amp; Computer Science.</p>

<p>Oct 2 of 2014 is our 1st year anniversary, and right now we are on skype while I&rsquo;m typing this blog.</p>

<p>She must not know the following project details as this will be my suprise gift for her.</p>

<p>I will launch a website with customized domain name, hosted on github. In the website, I will do some cool stuff (TBD, but have some cool ideas) to impress her. The website will be on <a href="http://wes-ivy.me">http://wes-ivy.me</a> , which currently redirects to this blog.</p>

<p>How likely she will find out about this intent? Hmm, statistically highly unlikely. She is just a normal girl who can&rsquo;t distinguish Mac OS &amp; iOS =P</p>

<p>This project will be a whole learning experience for me as well. I&rsquo;ve done Bootstrap before, but to really do what I have in mind requires far more than playing around.</p>

<p>I have 4 months, lets go and see.</p>

<p>Will post more updates later.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Post]]></title>
    <link href="http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/06/03/firstpost/"/>
    <updated>2014-06-03T11:27:09+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/06/03/firstpost</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Yes, this is actually my first post.</p>

<p>I was never meant to be a guy who keeps track of eveything in his daily life. I thought the first impression others could/should have are &ldquo;wtf&rdquo; or &ldquo;who cares&rdquo;. Sadly, it didn&rsquo;t change until recently thanks to one of my friends.</p>

<p>So, I started this, and as a &ldquo;brogrammer&rdquo; I believe it&rsquo;s right of me to &ldquo;code&rdquo; my blog rather than write my blog.</p>

<p>For those who don&rsquo;t have enough knowledge in programming or whats-so-ever (lucky you), I use octopress, github and sublime text 2 to make all this blog stuff happens (Ya, I know you have no idea what I&rsquo;m talking about =D).</p>

<p>To make it short, I wanna keep track of my life so at least I can have some references to write autobiography when I&rsquo;m too old to code and/or I can pull up some cool stuff as evidence when talking bs to my kids/grandkids (Hope world peace until then).</p>

<p>That&rsquo;s the whole point of this Journal/Blog/Diary stuff.</p>

<p>And, of cource, to practice English. Yes people, I know more than Java, Ruby, C++, Python and Javascript!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
