<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Journals | Nest]]></title>
  <link href="http://weshui.github.io/blog/categories/journals/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://weshui.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-09-11T00:27:31-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://weshui.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Wesley Hui]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[After Roadtrip]]></title>
    <link href="http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/09/11/after-roadtrip/"/>
    <updated>2014-09-11T00:13:03-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/09/11/after-roadtrip</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Well, it&rsquo;s been a while without blogging anything.
The reason for that is, of course, ROAD TRIP.</p>

<p>I have to keep this blogging thing away from my girlfriend. Otherwise, it won&rsquo;t be a suprise gift. Right?</p>

<p>Couple of updates.</p>

<blockquote><ol>
<li>California is a beautiful place.</li>
</ol>
</blockquote>

<p>I&rsquo;ve been to San Fransico and L.A before, but I didn&rsquo;t rent a car back then. This time, we rent car and visited Yosemite (yeah, next version of Mac OS X). In general, CA is an awesome place.</p>

<p>For those of you haven&rsquo;t get a chance to really appreciate CA, this video is good for you.</p>

<p><div class="embed-video-container"><iframe src="http://player.vimeo.com/video/105286558 "></iframe></div></p>

<blockquote><ol>
<li>I passed the interview, but no offer? What? Seriously?</li>
</ol>
</blockquote>

<p>I actually interviewed with CapitalOne for a Data Engineer role in their plano office. The first day after interview, my point of contact told me I passed the interview and congrats. Cool. But two days after, she said they need to make an exception to give me offer because my situation is not expected (OPT/F1). Well, why did you interview me in the first place?</p>

<blockquote><ol>
<li>New AppleEvent</li>
</ol>
</blockquote>

<p>Hmm, I will not get Apple Watch. 350$ for a not that impressive watch. Not worth it. But iPhone 6 is actually something. The power of NFC is &ldquo;Massive&rdquo; by one of my colleages. If Apple will release a NFC SDK, it will be Apple&rsquo;s Victory.</p>

<p>Lastly, I just want to see what&rsquo;s the reaction of my girlfriend once she sees this website.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[July/15]]></title>
    <link href="http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/07/15/july-slash-15/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-15T13:58:59-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/07/15/july-slash-15</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Finally visited Hogwarts and Diagon Alley and brought wand for myself.</p>

<p>As a loyal Harry Potter Serise fan, I gotta say Orlando trip was amazing. Well done Universal Studio.</p>

<p>Now, got back to deal with Hadoop stuff.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Upcoming Orlando Trip &amp; Misc]]></title>
    <link href="http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/06/24/upcoming-orlando-trip-and-misc/"/>
    <updated>2014-06-24T14:54:59-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/06/24/upcoming-orlando-trip-and-misc</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Booked our trip to Orlando the coming July 4th. Can&rsquo;t wait to see the &ldquo;refurbished&rdquo; Harry Potter Theme Park. I grew up reading Harry Potter series (countless nights in bed and thus shortsightedness). Finally get a chance to get myself a wand and drink butterbeer.</p>

<p>But, as always, you can&rsquo;t be happy and lucky all the time. Just turned down by Zillow for a Softwere Engineer Position. Well, I really like Seattle area and have a bunch of friends in there now. Too bad can&rsquo;t go there for on-site nor further career. A bit-manipulation interview question got me. I haven&rsquo;t use &amp; | ^ for years. Quite suprised that a well-known company actually will ask you this except the classic Two-Int-Exchange-Value question. Anyway, need to practice more on code.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Post]]></title>
    <link href="http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/06/02/firstpost/"/>
    <updated>2014-06-02T22:27:09-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/06/02/firstpost</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Yes, this is actually my first post.</p>

<p>I was never meant to be a guy who keeps track of eveything in his daily life. I thought the first impression others could/should have are &ldquo;wtf&rdquo; or &ldquo;who cares&rdquo;. Sadly, it didn&rsquo;t change until recently thanks to one of my friends.</p>

<p>So, I started this, and as a &ldquo;brogrammer&rdquo; I believe it&rsquo;s right of me to &ldquo;code&rdquo; my blog rather than write my blog.</p>

<p>For those who don&rsquo;t have enough knowledge in programming or whats-so-ever (lucky you), I use octopress, github and sublime text 2 to make all this blog stuff happens (Ya, I know you have no idea what I&rsquo;m talking about =D).</p>

<p>To make it short, I wanna keep track of my life so at least I can have some references to write autobiography when I&rsquo;m too old to code and/or I can pull up some cool stuff as evidence when talking bs to my kids/grandkids (Hope world peace until then).</p>

<p>That&rsquo;s the whole point of this Journal/Blog/Diary stuff.</p>

<p>And, of cource, to practice English. Yes people, I know more than Java, Ruby, C++, Python and Javascript!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
