<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Journals | Nest]]></title>
  <link href="http://weshui.github.io/blog/categories/journals/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://weshui.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-06-15T20:09:29-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://weshui.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Wesley Hui]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[On WWDC14]]></title>
    <link href="http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/06/04/on-wwdc14/"/>
    <updated>2014-06-04T17:50:06-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/06/04/on-wwdc14</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Finished the recap for WWDC 2014 yesterday. Didn&rsquo;t get a chance to write some of my thoughts on it until today.</p>

<p>Every summer, Google-Apple-Microsoft, the big 3 will host a serise of conferences to &ldquo;show off&rdquo; their latest work. Microsoft don&rsquo;t really draw a lot attention and I personally don&rsquo;t like its product (despite the fact that I do have a Nokia phone, but it does not run very smoothly and I don&rsquo;t appreciate that). So, it&rsquo;s quite interesting to watch Apple WWDC vs. Google I/O each year.</p>

<p>Despite its length (more than 2 hrs), I can see 3 major points from WWDC.</p>

<pre><code>Mac OS X Yosemite
iOS 8
Swift (not Taylor)
</code></pre>

<p>The following are my thoughts on each:</p>

<p>Start with <strong>Yosemite</strong>. I&rsquo;m not quite &ldquo;amazed&rdquo; by this except probably its name. (Dan, never been to Yosemite before but will do in this year.) Updates include a lot &ldquo;easier to use&rdquo; features. I will love the features like Mark for email and the new notification ctr where you can put widgets. But still, these new updates do not quite catch my eye when I was watching the video. It&rsquo;s Apple with Tim but only these updates this year? Not stress on performance/batter-life/compability? Well, let&rsquo;s wait and see then.</p>

<p><strong>iOS 8</strong> don&rsquo;t have a lot things as well. Honestly, group-chatting/file-sharing/voice-messge have been out there for years (Yes, I&rsquo;m talking about <a href="http://www.wechat.com/en/">WeChat</a>/QQ, which dominate China). I guess next step for iOS is to have it&rsquo;s own version of moment(a social sharing function built-in WeChat) maybe? One good thing is the tunnel between iOS and Mac OS X is finally opened. I&rsquo;ve been expecting this for quite a while. The continuity is not a quite new stuff. Last time I heard about this concept is from Netflix, where you can pick-up where you left on video across different platforms. And, it should work well with the large amount of Mac/iOS devices out there. What&rsquo;s next? Continuity on apps? Wait, this actually could work. You are welcome Apple.</p>

<p>Finally, <strong>Swift/DevCenter</strong>. As a developer, I gotta say Apple you did a great job here. The ability to use different services from different apps could make our lifes so much easier (both developer and consumer). And the new kits for Graphic looks so cool. 3D kit for casual game? Thats a good idea. Not to mention the new Swift language. Even tho it might be a little bit offend (I know what I&rsquo;m coding, thank you, I don&rsquo;t need to see it, just go away Swift!), but it definitely will help in most of the circumanstances. Wow, this new SDK is quite amazing! Can&rsquo;t wait to start writing my apps, but ya, need to read that 500 pages Swift book first&hellip;=P</p>

<p>And, last but not least, no words for iPhone 6. Gosh, I&rsquo;m waiting for a year but not a single word. (Don&rsquo;t look at me like this, Nokia. Maybe we should just be friends)</p>

<p>Let&rsquo;s see what Google I/O will bring =)</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Post]]></title>
    <link href="http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/06/02/firstpost/"/>
    <updated>2014-06-02T22:27:09-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/06/02/firstpost</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Yes, this is actually my first post.</p>

<p>I was never meant to be a guy who keeps track of eveything in his daily life. I thought the first impression others could/should have are &ldquo;wtf&rdquo; or &ldquo;who cares&rdquo;. Sadly, it didn&rsquo;t change until recently thanks to one of my friends.</p>

<p>So, I started this, and as a &ldquo;brogrammer&rdquo; I believe it&rsquo;s right of me to &ldquo;code&rdquo; my blog rather than write my blog.</p>

<p>For those who don&rsquo;t have enough knowledge in programming or whats-so-ever (lucky you), I use octopress, github and sublime text 2 to make all this blog stuff happens (Ya, I know you have no idea what I&rsquo;m talking about =D).</p>

<p>To make it short, I wanna keep track of my life so at least I can have some references to write autobiography when I&rsquo;m too old to code and/or I can pull up some cool stuff as evidence when talking bs to my kids/grandkids (Hope world peace until then).</p>

<p>That&rsquo;s the whole point of this Journal/Blog/Diary stuff.</p>

<p>And, of cource, to practice English. Yes people, I know more than Java, Ruby, C++, Python and Javascript!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
