<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Journals | Wes's Matrix]]></title>
  <link href="http://weshui.github.io/blog/categories/journals/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://weshui.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-03-05T20:54:27+13:00</updated>
  <id>http://weshui.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Wesley Hui]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Back to China!]]></title>
    <link href="http://weshui.github.io/blog/2015/03/05/back-to-china/"/>
    <updated>2015-03-05T20:46:42+13:00</updated>
    <id>http://weshui.github.io/blog/2015/03/05/back-to-china</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>It&rsquo;s been a while before I realize my last post was last year Nov 18.</p>

<p>I agree with you, I&rsquo;m lazy~</p>

<p>Anyway, many things happended over the past few mothes, and I would like to write them down (So I can refer to it years after).</p>

<ol>
<li><p>I got another gradute school admission offer from University of Wisconsin-Madison. TA position plus scholarship. Way better package thane the UCLA one. Yet, I have not decided where I should go for graduate school.</p></li>
<li><p>I decided to spend the next 6 months in Hangzhou China for the following reasons: a) I believe family is very important, b) my working authorization expired (which I could extend, but I didn&rsquo;t).</p></li>
<li><p>Before going back to China, I spent my past 10 days in New Zealand. Thats right, New Zealand, the first country to see the sunrise. In fact, this post is writen in Auckland International Airport, where I have 2 hours before boarding the plane to Shanghai.</p></li>
<li><p>I definitely will go back to U.S. for graudate school later this year. Which school? Not quite clear yet.</p></li>
</ol>


<p>I&rsquo;m back, China!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Grad School Admission]]></title>
    <link href="http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/11/19/first-grad-school-admission/"/>
    <updated>2014-11-19T08:17:08+13:00</updated>
    <id>http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/11/19/first-grad-school-admission</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Last week, I received my first grad school admission offer!</p>

<p>Master of Science in Computer Science admission from UCLA(for those who don&rsquo;t know, University of California Los Angeles!)</p>

<p>California, I&rsquo;m coming!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Anniversary]]></title>
    <link href="http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/10/03/first-anniversary/"/>
    <updated>2014-10-03T07:43:37+13:00</updated>
    <id>http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/10/03/first-anniversary</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>这篇文章是写给妹纸看的，所以还是用中文比较好。</p>

<p>亲爱的WZ姐姐</p>

<p><img class="right <a" src="href="https://fbcdn-sphotos-g-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xpa1/v/t1.0-9/10452355_555059154603770_5262808059192557325_n.jpg?oh=4e983214c699c84d7882ca7c4e299472&amp;oe=54C07048&amp;__gda__=1422391536_6caf5429b0c48a39ef82e5c3a0626294">https://fbcdn-sphotos-g-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xpa1/v/t1.0-9/10452355_555059154603770_5262808059192557325_n.jpg?oh=4e983214c699c84d7882ca7c4e299472&amp;oe=54C07048&amp;__gda__=1422391536_6caf5429b0c48a39ef82e5c3a0626294</a>" width="280" height="180">
下午工作的时候想起来，今天已经是10/2了。<br>
去年的这个时候，还是学生的我们在一起了。<br>
于是现在已经一年了。<br>
1年里，谢谢你的包容，理解，体贴（if any）。<br>
未来谁也不好说，但是不管在哪，2013年到2014年的这1年我肯定是不会忘记的。<br>
いろいろとありがとうございます!<br>
本来呢，打算这个网站的主页换成一个WebGL的动画的。<br>
但是吧，各种事情和GRE搞的我学习WebGL的过程异常的缓慢。<br>
不过呢，这个网站的网址就当我给你的礼物了。<br>
我自己注册的，是不是很厉害。<br>
顺带一提，ivy-wes这个也是我注册的，会重新导到这里来。<br>
明年的这个时候，WebGL应该可以完工啦，到时候记得来看哈。<br></p>

<p>最后，</p>

<p>周年纪念！<br>
Happy Anniversary！<br>
記念日おめでとう！<br></p>

<p>By Wesley Hui.<br>
All right reserved.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[After Roadtrip]]></title>
    <link href="http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/09/11/after-roadtrip/"/>
    <updated>2014-09-11T17:13:03+12:00</updated>
    <id>http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/09/11/after-roadtrip</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Well, it&rsquo;s been a while without blogging anything.
The reason for that is, of course, ROAD TRIP.</p>

<p>I have to keep this blogging thing away from my girlfriend. Otherwise, it won&rsquo;t be a suprise gift. Right?</p>

<p>Couple of updates.</p>

<blockquote><p>California is a beautiful place.</p></blockquote>

<p>I&rsquo;ve been to San Fransico and L.A before, but I didn&rsquo;t rent a car back then. This time, we rent car and visited Yosemite (yeah, next version of Mac OS X). In general, CA is an awesome place.</p>

<p>For those of you haven&rsquo;t get a chance to really appreciate CA, this video is good for you.</p>

<p><div class="embed-video-container"><iframe src="http://player.vimeo.com/video/105286558 "></iframe></div></p>

<blockquote><p>I passed the interview, but no offer? What? Seriously?</p></blockquote>

<p>I actually interviewed with CapitalOne for a Data Engineer role in their plano office. The first day after interview, my point of contact told me I passed the interview and congrats. Cool. But two days after, she said they need to make an exception to give me offer because my situation is not expected (OPT/F1). Well, why did you interview me in the first place?</p>

<blockquote><p>New AppleEvent</p></blockquote>

<p>Hmm, I will not get Apple Watch. 350$ for a not that impressive watch. Not worth it. But iPhone 6 is actually something. The power of NFC is &ldquo;Massive&rdquo; by one of my colleages. If Apple will release a NFC SDK, it will be Apple&rsquo;s Victory.</p>

<p>Lastly, I just want to see what&rsquo;s the reaction of my girlfriend once she sees this website.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[July/15]]></title>
    <link href="http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/07/16/july-slash-15/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-16T06:58:59+12:00</updated>
    <id>http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/07/16/july-slash-15</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Finally visited Hogwarts and Diagon Alley and brought wand for myself.</p>

<p>As a loyal Harry Potter Serise fan, I gotta say Orlando trip was amazing. Well done Universal Studio.</p>

<p>Now, got back to deal with Hadoop stuff.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
