<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Journals | Blank]]></title>
  <link href="http://weshui.github.io/blog/categories/journals/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://weshui.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2016-08-02T00:30:27-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://weshui.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Wesley Hui]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[wesely92@gmail.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Updates so far]]></title>
    <link href="http://weshui.github.io/blog/2016/06/16/updates-so-far/"/>
    <updated>2016-06-16T22:20:21-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://weshui.github.io/blog/2016/06/16/updates-so-far</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>It&rsquo;s been a year since my last update. Time does fly.</p>

<p>Just want to say I am still alive. Busy, but constantly learning new stuff.</p>

<p>Couple of things to &ldquo;brag&rdquo; about:</p>

<ul>
<li><p>Currently doing an Internship with Medallia in Palo Alto Bay Area, small (relatively speaking) company but people are really NICE!</p></li>
<li><p>Spent my last semester build a open source project database. Its initial version is about to be released (soon). Watch my Github account if you are interested in learning more.</p></li>
<li><p>Lost almost 20lbs so far</p></li>
</ul>


<p>Insipred by an <a href="http://aljun.me/">blogger</a>, I will start a series of tutorials  on topic like <strong>Machine Learning</strong> and <strong>Data Science</strong>. It should be a new learning experience on both ends.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Summer 2015 Internship/Part-time with Tencent]]></title>
    <link href="http://weshui.github.io/blog/2015/08/18/summer-2015-internship-slash-part-time-with-tencent/"/>
    <updated>2015-08-18T08:18:03-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://weshui.github.io/blog/2015/08/18/summer-2015-internship-slash-part-time-with-tencent</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>During the summer of 2015, I had this chance working with Tencent Hangzhou team. This journal will mainly be about this experience.</p>

<p>Tencent Hangzhou is a, relatively-speaking, small team. We had about less than 50 people working full-time. Yet, majority (all except 3 people) of them are developers. The main business done there are still CONFIDENTIAL (I signed the contract that I should not talk about it in public domain), yet I was surprised to find out that I could talk about my project (I guess that means my project is not important maybe?)</p>

<p>I did a <strong> Hadoop Version of Kmeans with Benchmark and Optimization </strong>.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Domain name expires]]></title>
    <link href="http://weshui.github.io/blog/2015/06/03/domain-name-expires/"/>
    <updated>2015-06-03T05:29:30-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://weshui.github.io/blog/2015/06/03/domain-name-expires</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Just realize my old domain name</p>

<h3>wes-ivy.me</h3>

<p>just expired.</p>

<p>Glad I have this back-up.</p>

<p>BTW, domain name 120usd/yr, what you think?</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Back to China!]]></title>
    <link href="http://weshui.github.io/blog/2015/03/04/back-to-china/"/>
    <updated>2015-03-04T23:46:42-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://weshui.github.io/blog/2015/03/04/back-to-china</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>It&rsquo;s been a while before I realize my last post was last year Nov 18.</p>

<p>I agree with you, I&rsquo;m lazy~</p>

<p>Anyway, many things happended over the past few mothes, and I would like to write them down (So I can refer to it years after).</p>

<ol>
<li><p>I got another gradute school admission offer from University of Wisconsin-Madison. TA position plus scholarship. Way better package thane the UCLA one. Yet, I have not decided where I should go for graduate school.</p></li>
<li><p>I decided to spend the next 6 months in Hangzhou China for the following reasons: a) I believe family is very important, b) my working authorization expired (which I could extend, but I didn&rsquo;t).</p></li>
<li><p>Before going back to China, I spent my past 10 days in New Zealand. Thats right, New Zealand, the first country to see the sunrise. In fact, this post is writen in Auckland International Airport, where I have 2 hours before boarding the plane to Shanghai.</p></li>
<li><p>I definitely will go back to U.S. for graudate school later this year. Which school? Not quite clear yet.</p></li>
</ol>


<p>I&rsquo;m back, China!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[First grad school admission]]></title>
    <link href="http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/11/18/first-grad-school-admission/"/>
    <updated>2014-11-18T11:17:08-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://weshui.github.io/blog/2014/11/18/first-grad-school-admission</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Last week, I received my first grad school admission offer!</p>

<p>Master of Science in Computer Science admission from UCLA(for those who don&rsquo;t know, University of California Los Angeles!)</p>

<p>California, I&rsquo;m coming!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
